

Game Programmer with experience developing mobile games for one year and have been using the Unity engine for 2 years. Understand design principles like composition over inheritance, and adopted data-driven design to easily create game levels. Learning about automization in games to increase efficiency. Love indie games, and love the indie industry even more.

# WORK EXPERIENCES

### Multimedia Developer

Mass Modules

2023 - Current

- · Developed 2 mini games accroding to the client's requirement.
- · Learned and interested in Kinect.

## Junior Programmer

Minidragon

2021 - 2022

- · Publish game events regularly with a team.
- · Run a Discord community with dozens active players and respond to their account issues, feature requests, bug reports;
- Profile the game to improve lags and freezings. Eg applying object pooling to UI game objects to remove freezing caused by loading.
- · Develop game features like an idle game mechanics to generate higher retention for the game.

### Unity developer (part-time)

2019 - 2020

Mint-asia

Develop an educational competitive game with a team of 5 members, using Photon.

# **CERTIFICATIONS**

#### CS50's Introduction to Game Development

Harvard University

2023

cs50q

Complete 12 projects, mostly using Löve 2D. Teach me about concepts like Entity Component System and designs like state stack, data-driven design.

#### CS50x

2022

Harvard University

cs50x

Complete 18 assignments and 1 final project, for learning from C, memory, data strctures, then Python and SQL, then ends with the Internet, web development and session.

# **PROJECTS**

Hectic Bins - A game originally made for a game jam - Ludum Dare 52. Got 112th out of 1641 submissions in the fun category as a result. Later ported to mobile and listed on Google Play.

Ninja Dash - Developed as a practice of applying design like SOLID and data-driven to a project. Improved game design sense as well.

GMO Forest - Educational game about DNA and RNA, using the genre tower defense as a media.

## Kenneth Yu

**Unity Programmer** 

kennethyu1224@outlook.com



<u>uyhtennek.github.io</u>



6315 6037

### **SKILLS**

Unity & C#

Git & GitHub

Lua, Python, JavaScript

Unity Gaming Service, Firebase

Flask, Django, node.js

## **EDUCATION**

**BSc in Multimedia** 

#### **LANGUAGES**

Cantonese (Native)